<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>I Miss Cover Flow</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2019-05-23T22:27:03+08:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Kevin Gu</name>
   <email>wxkevingu@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>A fresh beginning.</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/05/22/a-fresh-beginning/"/>
   <updated>2019-05-22T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/05/22/a-fresh-beginning</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As I claimed in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imisscoverflow.xyz/about/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;About Page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, having a personal blog set up is a long-wanted thing on my bucket list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the box is checked, finally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s always surprising to have all these years wasted in wanting a personal blog but doing literally nothing. Crystal clearly I know that anyone in dream of writing something on the Internet should have a blog running indepently from these babysitters even not being tech-savvy, period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moment finnaly came, I made up my mind that I should jump out of the trap set by Qzone and many other blogging-like service provider like Jianshu (but thumbs up for Medium), and of course, my laziness. And, really do something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;message&quot;&gt;Thankfully I started out, and I won't call it a miss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basic idea is to make this a place where I can have a rest, like, &lt;em&gt;a home on the Internet&lt;/em&gt;. It is expected that I will share new gadgets, trends, perspectives and thoughts on great works of liberal arts. If you see any older post, that would be my previous posts somewhere else(mostly in Chinese).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am grateful to those who provide tools that I used during the setting up of this blog. Also i would like to thank my friends, families and my girlfriend to keep me company during my looooong feeling down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Jeremy Clarkson said on his DriveTribe: &lt;em&gt;My Tribe, My Rules.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, &lt;em&gt;My Blog, My Rules&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
